What kinds of businesses do you think are going to succeed
because AI is so prevalent and people get tired of it?
I think the businesses that will have disproportionate returns
are ones that are very ops heavy.
So a marketing agency, for example,
that heavily introduces AI,
there will never be a lack of businesses
that want new customers.
The difficulty with scaling that particular type of business
is the operational drag and the headcount
and the coordination of people.
And so if you can have something
that has amazing product market fit,
which is get more customers for somebody,
there's lots of demand there.
But do it in a way that allows you to scale the ops
so that you have increasing margins
and you have less complexity,
that becomes incredibly valuable business.
So people heavy, ops heavy businesses
that are largely digital,
those are businesses that will benefit the most.